Guide to the Picture File, 1700s-1980s and undated RL.01025
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Stereographs Series, 1
  - Veterans carrying aloft their tattered flags. G.A.R. 1902. Washington, D.C., 1902, stereograph (Box Stereo 1, Folder S12)
  - [Jacksonville] "Upton's Florida Views," undated, 5 stereographs (Box Stereo 1, Folder S12)
    Included 1 card photograph removed to folder M120 in the Picture File Series.
  - Mandarin, Florida, undated, 4 stereographs (Box Stereo 1, Folder S13)
  - St. Augustine, Florida -- Cathedral, undated, 2 stereographs (Box Stereo 1, Folder S14)
    Transferred from the Trinity College Historical Society Relics.
  - St. Augustine, Florida -- City Gates, undated, stereograph (Box Stereo 1, Folder S15)
  - St. Augustine, Florida -- Entrance to Fort Marion, undated, stereograph (Box Stereo 1, Folder S16)
  - Cotton is King, Plantation Scene, Georgia, U.S.A., circa 1895, 3 stereographs (Box Stereo 1, Folder S17)
    Propaganda about cotton on back.
  - Toccoa Falls, undated, stereograph (Box Stereo 1, Folder S18)
    Removed to Stereographs Series from the same original folder as M164.
  - [Savannah] Georgia 1800s, 14 stereographs (Box Stereo 1, Folder S19)
  - [New Orleans] "Avenue of Live Oaks," Louisiana, 1800s, 2 stereographs (Box Stereo 1, Folder S20)
  - Shreveport, Louisiana, undated, stereograph (Box Stereo 1, Folder S21)
  - Grand Hotel, Saratoga Springs, New York, undated, stereograph (Box Stereo 1, Folder S22)
  - Land of the Sky Series -- W. D. Sprague's Hotel at Henry's Station, North Carolina, undated, stereograph (Box Stereo 1, Folder S23)
  - [Biblical locations and views], Palestine/Israel, 1899-1900, 9 stereographs (Box Stereo 1, Folder S24)
  - Charleston scenes, South Carolina, undated, 9 stereographs (Box Stereo 1, Folder S25)
  - Charleston -- Magnolia Cemetery, undated, stereograph (Box Stereo 1, Folder S26)
  - [Morris Island] Sea Front of Fort Wagner, South Carolina, circa 1865, stereograph (Box Stereo 1, Folder S27)
    This stereograph was originally foldered with the lithograph in folder M301.
  - Charleston, South Carolina, 1800s, stereograph (Box Stereo 1, Folder S28)
  - Arlington National Cemetery, Virginia, 1908, hand-colored stereograph (Box Stereo 1, Folder S29)
  - Petersburg -- The Crater, Virginia, 1874, stereograph (Box Stereo 1, Folder S30)
  - Richmond Bird's Eye View, Virginia, 1874 Apr. 26, 2 stereographs (Box Stereo 1, Folder S31)
  - Coal Wagons on Bridge, West Virginia, undated, stereograph (Box Stereo 1, Folder S32)
  - Yellowstone Park. Devil's Thumb and Liberty Cap, Wyoming, undated, stereograph (Box Stereo 1, Folder S33)
  - Away Down Among 'de Cotton and de Coons,' Louisiana, U. S. A., 1898, stereograph (Box Stereo 1, Folder S34)
  - Fifteenth Amendment Bringing His Crop to Town, 1800s, stereograph (Box Stereo 1, Folder S35)
  - Ripley, William Y. W. (family of), 1800s, 9 stereographs (Box Stereo 1, Folder S36)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, 1902, 18 stereographs (Box Stereo 1, Folder S37)
    Visit of President and Mrs. Roosevelt to the South Carolina Interstate and West Indian Exposition, Charleston, 1902. Transferred from the Hemphill Mss.
  - Tillman, Benjamin Ryan, undated, stereograph (Box Stereo 1, Folder S38)
    Transferred from the Hemphill Mss. Removed from M1656.
  - Sears, Roebuck and Company views, circa 1910, 50 stereographs (Box Stereo 1, Folder S39.1-10)
    Set of images originally packaged in box portrays buildings and grounds, departments, employee activities, and facilities at the Sears, Roebuck and Company headquarters in Chicago, Illinois, including the shipping, printing, and clerical departments, telephone switchboard, power plant, and other work areas. Transferred from the Rubenstein Library onsite stacks. Arranged in numerical order.